http://www.gulfportmemorial.com/privacy-policy

Home
I would like to...
Visitors
Cafeteria HoursContact NumbersDepartment of PharmacyFinancial AssistanceFind a LocationGift ShopHealth Info & Medical RecordsHospitalist ProgramMemorial Goes Tobacco Free!Memorial Hospital FoundationPastoral CareStudentsThe DAISY AwardVisiting HoursWiFi Now Available!
Patient
Portal
Health
Services
Cancer CenterDiagnostic Imaging CentersEmergency ServicesGastroenterology Health ServicesHeart ServicesLung Screening ProgramMemorial Care Coordination ProgramMemorial Hospital at Stone CountyNephrologyNeurosciencesNeurosurgeryOccupational Medicine Health ServicesOrthopedicsOutpatient RehabilitationSenior ServicesStroke CenterSurgical ServicesUrologyWellness ProgramsWomen & Children ServicesWoundCare
Walk-In
Clinics
Physician
Clinics
Phone and Video Visit
Allergies & ImmunologyCancer Center ClinicsEP CardiologyCardiothoracic SurgeryCardiologyDiagnostic Radiology / NeuroradiologyEndocrinologyFamily MedicineGastroenterologyGeneral SurgeryHeart Health & Cardiology
HospitalistInfectious DiseasesIntensivistInternal MedicineNephrologyNeurology ClinicsNeurosurgery ClinicsOccupational MedicineOncology/Hematology/MedicalOncology/RadiationOrthopedic SurgeryPain Management
PediatricsPhone and Video Visit
PodiatryPulmonologyRheumatologySurgical Services ClinicsThe Clinic at WalmartUrology ClinicsVascular SurgeryWalk-In ClinicsWoundCare Clinics
Locations &
Directions
Stone County LocationsFind a LocationMain Campus LocationDiagnostic Imaging LocationsWalk-In Clinics
Online Bill
Pay
Home»Policies & Ownerships»Privacy Policy
Section Menu...
Policies & Ownerships Home
• Editorial Policy• Privacy Policy• Notice of Privacy Practices• Patient Rights & Responsibilities
Policies & OwnershipsEditorial PolicyNotice of Privacy PracticesPatient Rights & ResponsibilitiesPrivacy Policy
Text Size:
Privacy Policy
Introduction.   We have created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and to disclose our practices in gathering, using and disclosing information in connection with this Web site. Personal information is information about a person that includes identifying information about that person. Although there are links from this Site to other Web sites, this Privacy Policy applies only to this Site and not to Web sites operated by others. For example, if you click on a link to the Web site of one of our partners or sponsors, the click takes you out of our Site. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other Web sites.
1.  Openness. We follow a general policy of openness regarding our privacy practices.  This Privacy Policy sets out the fair information practices that govern the collection, maintenance, use and disclosure of personal information regarding visitors who use this Site.
2.  Revisions to the Privacy Policy.  We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time as we add new features or as laws change that may affect our services.  If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post a new version number at the beginning of this Privacy Policy, consisting of the date (year and month)  the Policy was last revised, so that you will be able to tell when the Privacy Policy was last changed.
3.  Collection of Personal Information.  Except as disclosed in this Policy or as disclosed on other pages in this site where information may be collected, we do not collect personal information about visitors to this Site.
a.  Web logs.  We maintain standard Web logs that record data about all visitors who use this Site. These logs may contain:
i.  The Internet domain from which you access this Site (e.g., aol.com, abc.org);
ii. Your Internet Protocol (IP) address.  Your computer is automatically assigned a number which acts as its IP address when you surf the Internet.  Your IP address is either static (always stays the same) or dynamic (changes from time to time).  A static IP address may be identifiable to you, while a dynamic address is usually not identifiable.
iii. The type of browser and operating system you use.
iv. The date and time you visited the Site.
v. The pages that you saw on this Site.
vi. The address of the Web site you linked here from.
We use Web log information to help us design our Site, to identify popular features, and to make the Site more useful for visitors.  Web logs are recorded in sequential files, and we do not normally try to identify individuals from Web logs or use Web logs to gather information about individuals.  However, we may use Web logs to identify any person attempting to break into or damage our Site, and we may share Web log information with law enforcement agencies if we believe that we have evidence of a violation of computer security or related laws.
4.  Access, Correction, Deletion and Data Integrity.   Requests to access, correct or delete personal information may be submitted using our contact information.  Please note that we do not consider Web log information to be personal information. Also, we may not be able to delete or revise information about you that we have relied upon to provide services to you, or that we are legally required to maintain.
5.  Use and Disclosure of Personal Information.  We do not sell or rent personal information about visitors to this Site.  We do not use or disclose personal information obtained through this Site except as expressly described in this Policy.   No patient identifying information will be shared or transmitted on this Site.
a.  Uses.  We use information obtained from weblogs, cookies and visitor requests for the purposes described in this Policy. We use information obtained from this Site to respond to requests, improve our services, demonstrate the quality of our services to our auditors and government agencies that have authority over us, and for the additional purposes described below.
6.  Questions, Complaints or Requests to Change Information   If at any time you wish to contact us with a question or complaint or to exercise any of the rights set out in this Privacy Policy, or if you want to change any information collected by us, you may do so by contacting us by e-mail, telephone, or U.S. Mail, using the information set out below.
Contact Info:
E-mail: hdonegan@mhg.com
Phone: 228-867-5204
Mail: PO BOX 1810, Gulfport MS, 39502
Loading...
